https://tigg.com/about-us/privacy-policy/

About UsCore ValuesManufacturing CapabilitiesTestimonialsEventsCareersPrivacy PolicyMarket SectorsPFOA/PFOSMunicipal Drinking Water Treatment SystemsGroundwater Treatment TIGGManufactured Gas PlantWater FiltrationPCB RemovalSoil Vapor ExtractionVapor EmissionVapor Phase – Odor RemovalEquipmentLiquid Phase Adsorber Systems and EquipmentNSF/ANSI 61 CertificationVapor Phase Adsorber Systems and EquipmentLiquid and Vapor Activated Carbon Drum Filter UnitsUsed Activated Carbon Adsorber Systems and EquipmentIntegrated Activated Carbon Adsorber SystemsAncillary Equipment for AdsorbersActivated CarbonActivated Carbon Filter Media for Liquid Phase ApplicationsActivated Carbon Filter Media for Vapor Phase ApplicationsOil Absorption MediaMetals Removal MediaSand & Garnet for Cansorb Multi-Media FiltersServicesGranular Activated Carbon Adsorption Vessel ExchangeSpent Activated Carbon DisposalActivated Carbon Equipment RentalsResourcesPressContact Form 724-703-3020 1 Willow Avenue, Oakdale, PA 15071About UsCore ValuesManufacturing CapabilitiesTestimonialsEventsCareersPrivacy PolicyMarket SectorsPFOA/PFOSMunicipal Drinking Water Treatment SystemsGroundwater Treatment TIGGManufactured Gas PlantWater FiltrationPCB RemovalSoil Vapor ExtractionVapor EmissionVapor Phase – Odor RemovalEquipmentLiquid Phase Adsorber Systems and EquipmentNSF/ANSI 61 CertificationVapor Phase Adsorber Systems and EquipmentLiquid and Vapor Activated Carbon Drum Filter UnitsUsed Activated Carbon Adsorber Systems and EquipmentIntegrated Activated Carbon Adsorber SystemsAncillary Equipment for AdsorbersActivated CarbonActivated Carbon Filter Media for Liquid Phase ApplicationsActivated Carbon Filter Media for Vapor Phase ApplicationsOil Absorption MediaMetals Removal MediaSand & Garnet for Cansorb Multi-Media FiltersServicesGranular Activated Carbon Adsorption Vessel ExchangeSpent Activated Carbon DisposalActivated Carbon Equipment RentalsResourcesPressContact Form
Privacy Policy TIGG LLC - Activated Carbon Equipment, Media, and Services > Privacy PolicyWho we areOur website address is: https://tigg.com.What personal data we collect and why we collect itCommentsWhen visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.MediaIf you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.Contact formsCookiesIf you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.Embedded content from other websitesArticles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.AnalyticsHow long we retain your dataIf you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.What rights you have over your dataIf you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.  This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
